[opening theme song playing]
♪ Hey ♪
♪ Yo ♪
♪ Mmm-hmm, come on ♪
♪ Left the school behind
Into the world, a sign ♪
♪ Put the weights on a thrilling ride ♪
♪ Left the school behind
Into the world, a sign ♪
♪ Put the weights on a thrilling ride ♪
♪ Left the school behind
Into the world, a sign ♪
♪ Put the weights on a thrilling ride ♪
♪ Left the school behind
Into the world, a sign ♪
♪ Put the weights on a thrilling ride ♪
♪ Uh ♪
♪ Ow! ♪
♪ Oh-ooh, yeah ♪
♪ Yo ♪
- ♪ Come on ♪
- ♪ Move the world, move, move ♪
♪ Now, look, if I step into the world
We can have some fun ♪
♪ Yo ♪
♪ Uh, move the world, move, move ♪
♪ Now, look, if I step into the world
Let you have some fun ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Mmm-hmm, right ♪
- [squishing]
- [Legoshi grunting, panting]
[slurring] From now on... [panting]
I don't need fangs!
[fangs clatter]
Now with those out of the way,
I've earned the right
to give you a good punch!
- [yells]
- [Yahya grunts]
[breathes heavily]
[laughs]
I thought that it'd be worth it
to let it land.
[sighs] But what an utterly
pathetic strike.
If you meant for your punch to be
as weak as your personality, well done.
[grunts, spits]
[Yahya] Your fangs are gone,
but not your strength.
No, on the contrary, I see you rising.
Your spirit can carry you up
through the ranks of the carnivores
until you reign at the top.
[fire alarm ringing]
[chuckles]
It does appear we'll have some guests
from down below.
Huh?
[slurring] We carnivores
are also capable of reason,
and every one of us is suffering.
It just isn't right,
what you're trying to do.
I only punched you
because I was trying to make a point.
But I did disrespect the Beastar.
I am sorry for that.
I got to... I got to go.
[fire alarm ringing]
[receptionist] Mr. Yahya, I heard
the fire alarm. Is everything okay?
[Yahya sighs]
[Yahya] It's all right,
a candle fell over.
[ringing stops]
I am finding you
more and more intriguing, Legoshi.
THE GUY BORN IN SPRING
[Gohin, muffled] Try following my finger
with your eyes. Hmm?
Hey.
No good.
- [soft groaning]
- Can you hear me at least?
[groaning continues]
[Gohin] Hmm. There don't seem to be
any symptoms of Kines.
[panicked gasping]
- [Gohin] There you are.
- [gasping]
[chuckles] Take it easy, now.
I'm a doctor.
One famous for his radical treatments,
but still.
[chuckles]
Let's you and me try to get along, hmm?
- [soft groaning]
- Huh?
- Oh, you're awake.
- [Legoshi groans]
[muffled] Mr. Gohin?
Don't try to talk.
You're going to need a few days.
Huh? Huh?
- [muffled screaming, groaning]
- [laughing]
Oh, and don't touch your face.
- [gasping]
- Whoa now!
- [yelps]
- I'm warning you.
I won't go easy on you
just because you're a gal. Okay?
It could be worse, so don't be stupid.
- [spits]
- [grunts]
Hmm.
Seriously?
[amusing music playing]
Sorry about this,
but our rooms are all full right now.
- [pen rasping]
- [Gohin exhales]
WHAT DID THAT FOX DO?
Ah, devouring incident. Some rabbit.
[Legoshi] Mmm. Mmm.
You know, you gave me quite a shock,
collapsing at my front door
in such bad shape.
[scoffs] Who messed you up so bad?
[Legoshi] Mmm-hmm. Mmm.
I PULLED MY FANGS OUT
AND PUNCHED MR. YAHYA
Yahya? What?
What the hell are you doing,
picking a fight like that?
[Legoshi] Hmm.
I'LL WRITE UP A DETAILED REPORT
Spare me, I don't have
the time to read it.
I'm too damn busy dealing with
all these Kines patients anyway.
[Legoshi urging]
KINES IS A MEAT NARCOTIC!
Hmm? And you're certain of this?
[Legoshi] Mmm-hmm.
I'LL WRITE UP A DETAILED REPORT
[sighs] Fine.
In any case, rest here
until the swelling goes down, okay?
[Legoshi grunts]
[music ends]
[sighs]
GIANT PANDA
[Gohin] Hmm. Mornin'.
[grunts]
[sighs]
So, listen, there are two types
of devourers.
There's the type
that craves more meat afterward
and the type that feels too guilty
to want it again.
The treatment's different
depending on which type you are.
Why don't we talk about last night?
You devoured a living rabbit
in an alley off of Center Street.
Were they someone you knew?
[shuddering]
- Doctor... [shudders]
- Huh?
You know if you want me,
I'll let you take me.
- Hmm.
- Please, doctor.
- Wha--
- Please! Just do it!
Are you really that afraid
- to face up to what you've done? Huh?
- Come on! I'm begging you! [yelps]
[whimpering] Doctor! Just let me go!
Take me and be done with it!
- [Legoshi] Mmm.
- [Ai] I'm begging you! Please!
And screw you!
- Why are you doing this? Why?
- [Gohin] Hey! Listen to me!
Even if I was interested,
a roll in the hay with me
won't solve your problem.
It's important to understand
what made you do it.
If you can't figure that out,
your heart is going to hurt forever.
My heart's always going to hurt...
until I die?
That's right.
So what I want you to do
is take a deep breath and start trying
to come to terms with what you did,
even if the process
of getting there is hard.
[Legoshi sighs]
[Gohin] All right, tell me about yourself.
[Ai] Where do I start?
[Gohin] Wherever. I got all day.
[loudly] Huh?
What do you mean Yahya wanted you
to apologize for eating meat?
What's his deal?
Guess he's becoming more and more
of a stickler as he gets older.
You know, he had a partner
when he was younger.
Carrot and stick. Balanced each other out
like they were made for each other.
[Legoshi] Mmm.
[groans] Heard he was a piece of work.
Venomous monitor lizard
by the name of, uh...
[Legoshi] Hmm?
Go... hin. No, that would be me.
Gosha, yeah. That might've been it.
[Legoshi] Huh? My grandpa?
- Hmm.
- What is it?
I get it now.
Huh. That's why he was so strong.
Rumor has it
they had a fight and that was it.
Maybe things would be different
if that old lizard
were still around today.
Hmm.
What happened
between my grandpa and Yahya?
Hmm.
[Corne] I finally figured out
the location of the photo.
It's a multi-tenant building
on Center Street.
[Yahya] And was the ivory there?
[Corne] No. But I did notice
something strange.
When you overlay the floor plans
of each and every floor in this building...
Let's see... Oh, yeah, there it is.
This part.
No doors, no windows, just a space,
and it runs all the way down
to the basement.
Hmm.
That herbivore counselor's office
on the fifth floor...
[Corne] That is one big-ass sofa.
[Yahya] Zoom in on the fireplace.
Right on the floor.
Hmm. Now back to the fireplace.
Hold on.
Who's that on the right?
Oh, that's the counselor.
[Yahya] A gazelle, huh?
So the elephant lowers its guard
around a fellow herbivore.
They kill the elephant, drop the body
down the hole in the fireplace,
then cut it up in the basement.
That's when they remove the ivory
and prep it for sale.
That's their modus operandi.
But right in the middle
of a huge shopping district?
[Yahya sighs]
Is someone deliberately
trying to challenge me?
- [Gohin] Wow, you really are a big help!
- [Legoshi chuckles]
[slurring] Well, I am a stagehand.
Nah, it's more than touching up the paint.
- There was also the Kines report.
- [chuckles] You're really too nice.
I should honestly be apologizing.
I stayed for a whole week.
- [chuckles] Ah, Legoshi. Here.
- Hmm? Huh.
Huh?
[Gohin] These should help you
speak properly, and eat too.
Ah!
- Uh, thanks, but I don't need those.
- Huh?
I was serious
when I pulled out my own fangs.
It's not a decision
I intend to turn back from.
I don't need those replacements.
How are you going to eat?
I can live off rice porridge.
And how will you find yourself a girl?
I'll be a virgin all my life anyway.
[growling in frustration]
[sighs wearily]
Legoshi, I'm not saying
you have to wear 'em,
but at least try 'em on.
- [groaning]
- Legoshi!
If you're really going to be
that insistent, then I'll give 'em a try.
- [clicking]
- [Legoshi groaning softly]
[slurps, gulps]
[Gohin chuckles] Well?
[in normal voice] Huh. Honestly,
they feel just right. [chuckles]
[sighs]
I wanted to be strong
without having to use my fangs.
That's the whole reason
I was training under you.
[inhales, exhales]
And the way things shook out,
you managed to win
a life-or-death fight against a bear
only by eating your friend's leg.
If you've come this far already,
why not accept yourself
as the wolf you are?
Okay, so, after seeing
Yahya's overwhelming presence,
the first place I thought to run to
was the Black Market.
If I have subconsciously let this place
become my safe space, then...
doesn't that make me a hypocrite?
If that's really how you feel right now,
I encourage you to spend some time
thinking it through.
Right. [sighs softly]
Thank you very much.
[Gohin exhales]
[mellow piano music playing]
Tibetan sand foxes
have a reputation for not showing
their emotions on their face.
Made it hard to tell if you were ready.
I was a challenge, but even then,
you chose to fight through and help me.
It was only as I regained my emotions
that I realized that.
You've been working hard, Ai.
But the more time
I spent with you, doctor,
the more I could feel my guilt
weighing me down.
It sounds to me like you're not at risk
of devouring someone ever again.
- [Ai] Doctor?
- Hmm?
I'm going...
to turn myself in to the police.
[Gohin breathes heavily]
[sobbing]
Hey now.
That's emotion,
but I wish it were a smile.
You're the one who should be smiling.
You said the best route is for the patient
to turn themselves in, right?
Well, may be best for society.
Still, for now,
you'll just have to let me be sad.
Then I'm going to leave my smile
with you for a while.
Hmm?
I'll leave you with a smile, and you can
give it back to me when I get out.
Well? What do you say
we call it a promise?
[laughs]
It would have to be a fantastic smile
for me to agree to that.
[Ai chuckles softly]
[Gohin] Come back soon, okay?
PLANT PRODUCTION RESEARCH FACILITY
[Haru] Wow. [chuckles]
This university
really does have everything.
[Lisa] You mean for the plants?
You sure love them, don't you, Haru?
- Huh? Do you not?
- It's not that.
I only enrolled here because I heard
it helps when looking for a job.
What about you?
Well, I want to open a restaurant.
- Seriously?
- That's right.
I want to serve vegetables
that carnivores will find delicious too.
- What?
- Well, think about it.
If everyone could share the same meals,
wouldn't that be fun?
Honestly, that's sort of what
I'm hoping to study here.
You really are something else, Haru.
You know that?
Hello there, new students.
Allow me to welcome you to today's lesson
on edible plants and taste.
- [chuckles]
- [pigeon] Yeah.
I... I see that you're all herbivores.
Very good. [chuckles]
We won't have
any of those nasty brutes in here,
stinking up our beautiful plants.
Thank God.
- [students chuckle]
- Huh? Hmph.
And as our first topic,
we herbivores possess far more
refined palates than carnivores do.
There are flavors we enjoy that carnivores
are unable to even begin to detect.
Their palates are as barbaric as they are.
[exclaims in disappointment]
- You're being discriminatory.
- Huh?
[all gasp]
My boyfriend tells me how hurt he is
by that sort of casual hate speech.
It's inappropriate
in a so-called place of higher learning.
Uh, that's true.
How right you are. [nervously]
Do forgive me.
You're dating a carnivore?
You should really try it for yourself.
You'd be amazed at how it opens your eyes.
[pigeon] Let's try to start this lesson
on the right foot.
[Ako] Hmm.
[Lisa] Ako, you're just amazing.
- You were so cool back there.
- Well? What happened? I want to hear.
Not a lot. I just told the professor that
his way of thinking is so last century.
People see love between carnivores
and herbivores as dangerous,
but if a couple understands each other
as well as we do, it can totally work out.
- [Haru] You shouldn't say that so lightly.
- [scoffs] Huh?
If it truly were that easy,
if simply understanding
was all a relationship needed,
then our society wouldn't have to
deal with so many devouring incidents.
I don't know if you just haven't
realized it yet, but...
the heart can't overcome instinct.
Can you truly love him fully
even when his body
continues to crave meat?
I've been wondering about you.
The only reason you're dating
in the first place
is to make a fashion statement, right?
[Ako] Excuse me?
[quirky music playing]
[Eado] Hey, wait up!
I get you're mad,
but don't take it out on me.
I don't get why you're not mad too.
You could have given her a growl
or scared her or something.
Instead, you let her embarrass us.
Look, I don't really...
Hey, are you angry
because she saw through us like that?
- That we're dating to make a statement?
- What?
I mean, we're both
kind of messing around here.
There's no need to be
so upset about it, is there?
- Eado.
- Huh?
In the end, you're just another
ordinary lion, aren't you?
Just because you can't see me,
a rabbit, as a female, you can't commit.
If you really think I'm wrong,
then prove it. Give me a kiss!
[chuckles nervously]
[sighs] Well, if you insist.
[Ako moans softly]
[gasps]
Uh-- What do you know, you can commit.
No ordinary lion would dare
turn down a challenge like that.
[mysterious music playing]
[Melon, muffled] Not to worry,
our facilities were built
to accommodate all species,
including elephant patients like yourself.
[elephant] I can't tell you how grateful
I am to talk to an herbivore therapist.
[Melon] No, no.
[elephant] I know that some may
find myself as intimidating,
but at the end of the day,
I'm still an herbivore like you.
- Uh, so, um, I hope...
- [Yahya grunts]
[Melon] Oh, no, it's all right.
Just take your time
and tell me everything when you're ready.
[elephant crying]
- [Yahya] Hmm.
- [Melon] There, there.
- [Yahya grunts]
- [elephant crying]
- [elephant] I'm so sorry.
- Huh?
- I'm crying.
- [Melon] It's all right.
[elephant] I just think that I... [sobs]
[groans]
- [Melon] Do you have an appointment?
- [groans]
That's so odd,
I must have missed it in my calendar.
But, you know,
I think I can squeeze you right in.
But I'm afraid personal items
must be left at the front desk.
I know exactly what you really are.
[Melon, sarcastically] Wow!
A Beastar knows who I am!
[laughs sarcastically] What an honor.
- [grunts]
- [mask snaps]
[gasps]
Wait, are you--
Oh, I guess you don't know me.
The name's Melon.
- [grunts]
- Remember it.
[groans, sighs]
[groans]
Ah, we finally get to meet.
[inhales sharply]
- But now I can't invite you to the party.
- [groaning]
- Shame.
- [grunts]
[yelps] Get back!
[grunts, yelps]
- [thuds]
- [groans loudly]
[music ends]
- [indistinct chatter]
- [Haru] Oh, me and my big mouth.
To be fair, I don't think
I said anything that wasn't true.
But calling my friend's relationship out
in public like that?
Oh, I'm the worst.
I, uh, was probably just jealous.
They seem to be having fun
as a mixed-species couple.
- [sighs] I should tell Ako I'm sorry.
- [siren wails]
- [goat] What's going on?
- [Haru] Huh?
- [tiger] Sounds like it's bad.
- [siren wails]
[indistinct chatter]
- [Eado] Ako!
- [officer] Get back!
[Eado sobbing]
- [gasps]
- [Eado] I don't know what happened.
- [Eado sobbing]
- [Ako breathing feebly]
I don't... I just...
- [breathing feebly]
- [Haru gasps softly]
I just kissed her
'cause she told me to. [breathes heavily]
I swear I didn't want to eat her!
But I... I just got confused! [sobbing]
- Hey.
- Please! You got to save her! Please!
- [officer 1] Get in there!
- Ako!
[officer 1] Shut up!
- [officer 2] Calm down.
- Ako!
- [car door closes]
- [Haru] The ground is covered in blood.
But today is such a beautiful, sunny day.
[dog] Oh. Watch yourself young lady.
Sorry, it'll leave a stain
if we don't clean it now.
[Haru] Can you love him fully
even when his body
continues to crave meat?
I knew it from the start.
To truly love a carnivore
is to enter a world of pain and suffering.
It's not something simple,
made up of low stakes and little jokes.
But that's why...
That's exactly why I...
[gasps]
[yells]
UDON BEBEBE
[newscaster] At around 3:00...
Sorry about the wait.
...an attempted devouring took place
on the campus of Algama University.
- The student was...
- [Legoshi] Haru's school.
...taken from the scene
in critical condition.
But it does seem as though
they're going to pull through.
Huh?
Hey, Legoshi. Happy birthday.
Uh, I just wanted to say that,
so I came by.
[closing theme song playing]
♪ Just like a new melody ♪
♪ Keep it beating on and on ♪
♪ I don't want to live without it ♪
♪ You give me the strength inside ♪
♪ Some things aren't meant to be ♪
♪ You say it like you know ♪
♪ But I really want you ♪
♪ I want you to see it the way I do ♪
♪ 'Cause every time I think about you ♪
♪ My heartbeat goes a-risin' ♪
- ♪ And I just want to feel like this ♪
- ♪ Run, run, run ♪
- ♪ Till I... ♪
♪ Till I die ♪
♪ There's nothing
That can beat like this ♪
♪ Faster as I close my eyes ♪
- ♪ Just want to feel like this ♪
- ♪ Run, run, run ♪
- ♪ Till the... ♪
♪ Till the night ♪
♪ Now as long as you are here by my side ♪
♪ Run, run, run ♪
♪ I keep walking on ♪
♪ Walking on, on, walking on, on ♪
- ♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
- ♪ Walking on, on, walking on, on ♪